<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="//www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Bobby L. Craig</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <updated>2017-07-12T22:09:51-04:00</updated>
 <author>
   <name>Bobby L. Craig</name>
   <uri>https://bobbylcraig.com</uri>
   <email>bobbylcraig@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Dylan Got Married!</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/06/17/dylan-got-married.html"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/06/17/dylan-got-married</id>
   <updated>2017-06-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Quick update: during the spring my friend Dylan notified me that he was getting married and invited me to attend his wedding. I knew I’d be in Atlanta for the summer and his wedding was in Pennsylvania, so it’d be tough, but eventually I made it work with plane tickets...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>I Caved</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/06/16/i-caved.html"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/06/16/i-caved</id>
   <updated>2017-06-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It didn’t take me too long of being in a city alone to finally cave and recreate my Instagram. I’m still going strong without Snapchat, but Instagram is a killer. Better yet, my account actually got deleted so I have to start over from scratch. This’ll be…interesting. However, while I...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Concert in the Park</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/06/15/concert-in-the-park.html"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/06/15/concert-in-the-park</id>
   <updated>2017-06-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I decided to go running in Piedmont Park near my apartment today, and I was welcomed with a wonderful surprise. I entered the park and made my way through one of the winding paths when I happened upon hundreds of people and a large concert stage set up. I was...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>I Got My First Freddie</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/06/13/got-my-first-freddie.html"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/06/13/got-my-first-freddie</id>
   <updated>2017-06-13T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I suppose you could say it’s been a pretty good week (aside from the Cavs losing the finals…pfft). I’ve gotten to know the other interns at MailChimp much better, I have been getting into a rhythm and living a decently healthy lifestyle, and I even won a scavenger hunt (and...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Four Days In Atlanta</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/06/07/4-days-here.html"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/06/07/4-days-here</id>
   <updated>2017-06-07T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It’s Wednesday. I’ve been in Atlanta for four days, and I’m absolutely loving my time here. MailChimp is a really great company—I’m really missing my co-workers from Tenable though… I’m hoping to make relationships at MailChimp like I made at Tenable. I came in a little later than most of...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Mostly Done With Abroad Blog</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/06/06/mostly-done-with-abroad-blog.html"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/06/06/mostly-done-with-abroad-blog</id>
   <updated>2017-06-06T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;So, it’s not entirely official, but I’ve sent out the link to a few people for my abroad blog. I’ve mostly finished the writing (aside from some editing because I’m a bit too lazy to read my own writing…it takes a long while) and the design is mostly done. I’m...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>I Have Moved Into Atlanta</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/06/04/moved-into-atlanta.html"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/06/04/moved-into-atlanta</id>
   <updated>2017-06-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have officially moved into Atlanta. I’m interning with MailChimp this summer, and I’m super excited to get started. The weather is rather warm and humid here, but I’m sure it won’t take me too long to get adjusted. I can’t wait to meet the other interns—my roommate Garrett seems...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>I Deleted My Social Media</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/05/30/deleted-social-media.html"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/05/30/deleted-social-media</id>
   <updated>2017-05-30T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In a (probably) impulsive fashion, I decided to delete practically all of my social media (I kept Facebook because I need it for groups). This means that I deleted Twitter, Instagram, Snapchat, and anything else I deemed necessary. I did this for several reasons.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;It's distracting. Although I still...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Cool Story About Recent Ransomware Attack</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/05/19/accidentally-stopping-major-ransomware-attack.html"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/05/19/accidentally-stopping-major-ransomware-attack</id>
   <updated>2017-05-19T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Just check out the link below. Pretty interesting/funny stuff… not exactly so “accidental”.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Taylor Room Layout</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/05/02/taylor-room-layout.html"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/2017/05/02/taylor-room-layout</id>
   <updated>2017-05-02T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Here at Jacobs, boredom does interesting things to me. One of those things happens to be that it makes me think of the future—specifically, my time at Denison. I’m rooming with Oliver next year and figured I’d give a try at creating our room layout (of course nowhere near what...</content>
 </entry>

 

</feed>